### Tina Zhao

( ☐ tinaz@tuta.io ) ( ⊕ manacake.co ) ( ⊕ San Francisco, CA )

### **Summary**

Tina is a full-stack engineer with extensive experience in web, mobile, and embedded hardware application development. She is familiar with the fast-paced dynamic of startups and is regarded as a self starter and a team player. She is also a well-organized multi-tasker with superb interpersonal skills and creative spunk!

### **Skills**

Languages	Javascript/Node, Python, C, C++, Go, Ruby, Agda, Scala
Platforms	AWS, Google Cloud, Heroku, Shopify
Frameworks	Vue, React, Express, Electron, Django
Templating	Liquid, Handlebars, EJS
Web	HTML, S/CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Material Design
Other	PostgreSQL, PlatformIO, Nginx, Git, Sketch, Photoshop

### **Experience**

Head of Software Engineering Outset ( ⊕ greycat.co )

- Designed, wrote, and maintained all versions of firmware for custom printed circuit board
- Implemented a security protocol to send encrypted data through public airspace
- Reverse engineered the control of integrated circuits via datasheets and troubleshooting

Developer (Oct 2015 - Dec 2017)

Next Thing Company (Oakland, CA)

- Wrote and maintained the primary shipping logistics and customer pre/order management system responsible for delivering product inventory to customers worldwide
- Designed web/native app that allowed customers to flash OS images to computers
- Created and managed e-commerce store and all client facing web presences
- Built plugin to calculate various courier shipping charges for e-commerce shop
- Illustrated and designed image assets for apps and UX flows in production

(continued...)

Developer (Sep 2014 - Oct 2015)

## **Prompt.ly** (San Francisco, CA)

- Designed and implemented UI/UX for company app on mobile and web
- Wrote and maintained key features of app including payments, subscriptions, locations
- Created scripts to supply company with critical analytics and marketing data
- Built and maintained scrapers to gather qualified leads to grow customer base
- Migrated and refactored app's vanilla CSS to Sass
- Collaborated with executive and engineering leadership to analyze and plan sprints
- Trained new team members on stack tech as part of the on boarding process
- Participated in regularly reoccurring focus groups of app users to gather feedback

Web Developer (Aug 2008 - Sep 2014)

# West Wind Education Policy, Inc. (lowa City, IA)

- Illustrated and designed image assets for use in conventions, grant proposals, presentations and print material for state level department of education clients
- Turned client deliverables into interactive web apps
- Provided upkeep on client facing web spaces and company client database
- Maintained social networking accounts for client projects

#### **Education**

B.A. Computer Science, May 2014 University of Iowa

A.A. Business Administration, May 2010 Kirkwood Community College

Japanese, Aug 2005 - June 2007 University of California Davis